const ComputerBasicsQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What is the main processing unit of a computer?",
        options: ["Central Processing Unit", "Random Access Memory", "Graphics Processing Unit", "Solid State Drive"],
        correct_option: "Central Processing Unit"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a primary input device?",
        options: ["Monitor", "Printer", "Speakers", "Keyboard"],
        correct_option: "Keyboard"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the most common output device of a computer?",
        options: ["Printer", "Keyboard", "Mouse", "Monitor"],
        correct_option: "Monitor"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following stores data temporarily in a computer?",
        options: ["ROM (Read-Only Memory)", "HDD (Hard Disk Drive)", "SSD (Solid State Drive)", "RAM (Random Access Memory)"],
        correct_option: "RAM (Random Access Memory)"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the basic unit of digital information?",
        options: ["Byte", "Kilobyte", "Megabyte", "Bit"],
        correct_option: "Bit"
    },
    {
        question: "Which computer component holds the operating system and software programs?",
        options: ["Solid State Drive", "RAM (Random Access Memory)", "Motherboard", "Hard Disk Drive"],
        correct_option: "Hard Disk Drive"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the function of a motherboard in a computer?",
        options: ["Stores data permanently", "Processes instructions", "Displays output", "Connects all computer components"],
        correct_option: "Connects all computer components"
    },
    {
        question: "Which type of software provides a user interface for interacting with the computer?",
        options: ["Antivirus", "Word Processor", "Web Browser", "Operating System"],
        correct_option: "Operating System"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of an operating system in a computer?",
        options: ["Creates documents", "Displays graphics", "Provides internet connectivity", "Manages hardware resources"],
        correct_option: "Manages hardware resources"
    },
    {
        question: "Which computer component processes graphics and images?",
        options: ["Central Processing Unit (CPU)", "Random Access Memory (RAM)", "Solid State Drive (SSD)", "Graphics Processing Unit (GPU)"],
        correct_option: "Graphics Processing Unit (GPU)"
    }
];

export default ComputerBasicsQuestions;
